Hey, everybody. Back for more.
Actually, sorry, I forgot to change
the section of the textbook
before I started recording. Hey,
everybody. Back for more content
about NumPy and NumPy arrays.
So this is section 7.4 of your
textbook, filling arrays with specific
values. So what if, hypothetically,
you wanted to just create an empty
array or you wanted to create an
array that had nothing in it and then,
you know, fill it with specific
stuff? So I think I maybe mentioned
that there's other sections of this
textbook that you could read through
to kind of like learn a little bit
more about these specific things,
arrays. But we're going to jump to
filling these arrays with, sorry,
filling them with specific
values. And specifically,
we're going to talk about
NumPy zeros and NumPy ones.
um so numpy or arrays are kind of
weird and you can add things to
them um and and take things away
kind of like you can do with a
built-in python list um but what
they like you to do initially is
to kind of set how big your array
is going to be before you start
um adding things to it and this
is kind of all detailed in section
7.3 I'm not going to spend a ton
of time going through that but
but generally speaking it's like
this is how big the array is
going to be this is what we want
what we want to work with so you
can create numpy arrays with zeros
and ones and then you can alter
it after that point. So what
you'll do to initialize this array
is import NumPy and let's call
this NumPy 1. Here's an array,
we'll set it equal to numpy dot
zeros and we'll fill it with a
hundred zeros and then let's just
print that out to the console.
So that doesn't look like a
hundred but it is. And there's
also another function called
numpy1s, which works the same way.
See here,
and that will help you to create
your arrays. So we'll talk a
little bit more about these in
another content video, but that's
everything for this content
video, so thanks for watching.